Good afternoon Good afternoon I am from Ukraine, the
добрый день Добрый день Я из Украины
city of Khmelnitsky And you are
город Хмельницкий А вы
from Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky Where are you from
из Украины город Хмельницкий Вы откуда
?
где-то сейчас на войне в Украине или нет
peaceful form,
нельзя носить военную форму мирным
it’s true, they
это правда
gathered for fishing, for this they chose
собрались на рыбалку для этого выбрали
Ukraine
Украину
Let’s ask what you wanted to
Давайте спрашивать что вы хотели
ask the Ukrainians
украинцев спросить
[music]
[музыка]
and you are Russian I don’t look like a Russian
а вы русский Я на русского похож нет А
Why are you so interested in Russophobia
чего Вас так интересует русофобии
interesting well, look at the people who
интересно ну смотрите людей которые
attack our country no one loves
нападают на нашу страну никто не любит
absolutely And when  our Russophobia was
абсолютно И когда у нас русофобия была
at a low level before the attack now it is
на небольшом уровне до атаки сейчас она
very
очень большом
high you even have flasks I see in the background
у вас даже флаки смотрю на заднем фоне
there is Why don’t you take don’t put on a
есть А почему вы не возьмете не оденете
uniform don’t volunteer for the army I
форму не пойдете добровольцам в армию Я
’m just like you I have
просто я просто как и вы на рыбалку
to go fishing now Well fine
сейчас должен сходить Ну прекрасно У
I don’t have a brother’s pea jacket, you understand
меня нету бушлата братовского понимаете
good brothers,
хороших братьев
a lot of Chechens are not Kadyrov, but
очень много чеченцев не Кадыров а
Chechens
чеченцев
against Russia,
против России
your Look and see  our rare ones fought against
ваши Смотри и ваши редкие воевали против
Russia for
России
all the centuries Russia captured Imam
все Столетия Россия захватила Имам
Shamil you know who he is Well of course of
Шамиль знаете кто такой Ну конечно
course you know yes that's how you think he
конечно знаете да вот как вы считаете он
would submit to Russia
покорился бы России
I think that in the first place it's not for you
Я думаю что в первую очередь это не вам
to argue caught no So why
надо рассуждать поймала нет Так почему
Because if you take the account that we
Потому что если вы берете счет что мы
spoke with Russia So let's be
говорили с Россией Так давайте будем
frank that you are kafir that they are kafirs
откровенными что вы кафир что они кафиры
so it’s not for you on this topic now it
так что не вам на эту тему сейчас
turns out you
получается вы
are working for kafers like
на каферов типа работаете
I say I’m fishing your people who are
Я говорю я на рыбалку ваши люди которые
not fishermen
не рыбаки
they are all I only answer for myself I
они все я за себя только отвечаю
didn’t open much didn’t say it
не открывали много не говорили
turns out  that Russia was like that in the 90s of the
получается что Россия так в 90-х годах
first Chechen second Chechen
первой чеченской второй чеченской
How much it destroyed now
Сколько уничтожила сейчас
on the Internet
в интернете
That's how the Chechens should say the
Вот так надо говорить чеченцами выходит
fisherman goes out to fish
Рыбак на рыбу пойдёт
and when you ask Him the right
брата и когда Ему задаешь правильные
questions That
вопросы Что
How many of your brothers Russia killed
Сколько твоих собратьев убила Россия
never, not even never Imam
никогда то даже не даже никогда Имам
Shamil was there  that's literally and 30 back
Шамиль там было вот буквально и 30 назад
25 or how much it was
25 или Сколько было
and the dude freezes because he can't
и чувак подвисает потому что он не может
say anything
сказать ничего
he either b  oits to speak
он либо боится до говорить
or absolutely understands everything and cannot
либо все абсолютно понимает и не может
say it simply cannot because he
сказать просто не может потому что у
has no words how many Chechens Russia killed
него нет слов сколько Россия убила
how many killed
чеченцев сколько убила
not only those who
не только тех даже которые
fought for the independence of ordinary people
воевали за независимость обычных людей
that the main thing is that
жизней унесло самое что основное что
Russia is the
Россия
Russian
русские
Chechen people
чеченский народ
and these Chechens, instead of
и вот эти чеченцы вместо того чтобы
raising even non-Chechens Kadyrov
поднимать даже не чеченцев Кадыров
Chechens different things, these Kadyrovites are not
чеченцы разные вещи эти кадыровцы не
instead of raising the Banner of struggle
вместо того чтобы поднимать Знамя борьбы
for their independence They serve Russia,
за свою независимость Они служат России
they go Like cannon fodder somewhere in a
они идут Как пушечное мясо куда-то в
foreign country to die for  the interests of the Kremlin, the
чужую страну погибать за интересы Кремля
interests of that clique that killed their
интересы той клики которые убивала их
fathers and grandfathers, and when normal Chechens
отцов дедов и когда нормальные чеченцы
Which
Которые
of these persecutions were supposed to
из этих преследований должны были там
leave there or go to Ukraine in Europe
выехать или там в Украину в Европу
are waging a political military struggle against
ведут военную борьбу политическую против
Russia, they unite in some kind
России объединяется в какие-то
of anti-Russian organizations, they go this
организации антироссийские они идут это
resistance as best they can But  these
сопротивление каждый как может А вот эти
sit
сидят
and they go  the ear meat of the empire,
и они идут Как пушечное мясо империи
you understand, this is the
понимаете это
age when there is the Internet, when you can
век когда есть интернет когда можно
see whatever information you want,
посмотреть что хочешь какую информацию
not only that they were taken there to
не то что их там забрали в какой-то
some village somewhere where there was no
села какого-то где не было там
TV, radio, they were taken to the front,
телевидение радио забрали на фронт
now they all understand everyone sees their
кинули сейчас они все понимают все видят
whole history  I know
всю историю свою знаю
[music]
[музыка]
illustrates how a
иллюстрирует как
proud people pride freedom-loving
гордый народ гордость свободолюбивый
people can be broken can be
народ можно преломить можно сделать
done with this
вот этим гнетом
imperial oppression so put some kind of
имперским так поставить какого-то
boss like Kadyrov there who
начальника типа там Кадырова который
will keep their fears there
будет там держать их страхи
and other nations are enslaved by Russia also
и другие нации порабощены России также
just on the Chechens this is very
просто на чеченцах это очень ярко
pronounced because  they suffered in the 90s
выраженное видно потому что они в 90-х
from Russia Chechnya in 90
пострадали до от России Чечня в 90 году
declared its Independence what
объявила своей Независимости какие
other republics
другие до республики
left the Soviet Union before the republic, too,
выходе там из Советского Союза тоже
and as a result Yes, in the nineties the first
и в результате Да в девяностых первая
Chechen war The second Chechen war
чеченская война Вторая чеченская война
how many proud sons of the
сколько гордых сыновей
Chechen people Russia destroyed
чеченского народа уничтожила Россия
How the Chechens are treated
Как относятся
Yes here  these Russians are Russian
чеченцам Да вот эти россияне русский
I don't know how to explain it what should
Я не знаю как это объяснить что должно
make  there is a
заставить
guy in a peacoat, a fisherman,
ребят парня в бушлате рыбачка
so that instead of going somewhere to
чтобы он вместо того чтобы ехал куда-то
die for the Empire and die gloriously,
умирать за Империю и славно умирать
so that he alone, like-minded people
чтобы он его одно единомышленники
raise the flag of the struggle for their
поднимали флаг борьбы за свою
independence
независимость
like this,
вот так
like this, expand the information about the
Ставьте лайк расширит информацию про
video, we are little Crocos, we are accessible to the
видео мы маленькие Кроко мы доступны до
minds of millions of people Glory  Ukraine
разума миллионов людей Слава Украине
Ichkeria bodibil
Ичкерия бодибил